Guide to the Arthur H. Landis Oral History Collection ALBA.AUDIO.066
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Miscellaneous Reel-to-Reel Audiotapes, 1945-1970.
  - Unrelated to Landis Book Project: Bart Van der Schelling, [June 1969?]; cuid43104 (Box 2, Audiocassette 66- 66, Box 5, Cd 66- 66)
    Duration: 63 minutes; Preservation note: 1/2 track captured in one pass. Track 2 had to be digitally reversed.
  - Unrelated to Landis Book Project: Bart Van der Schelling (I), Feb 1970; cuid43105 (Box 2, Audiocassette 66- 67, Box 5, Cd 66- 67)
    Duration: 32 minutes
  - Unrelated to Landis Book Project: Bart Van der Schelling (II), Feb 1970; cuid43106 (Box 2, Audiocassette 66- 68, Box 5, Cd 66- 68)
    Duration: 65 minutes; Preservation note: 1/2 track captured in one pass. Track digitally reversed. At the 00:16:30;xx mark of track 2, the content changes and there is a drastic lowering of the volume (digitally corrected for the access file)
  - Unrelated to Landis Book Project: Bart Van der Schelling: Singing, Oct 1964 (Box 2, Audiocassette 66- 69, Box 5, Cd 66- 69)
  - Unrelated to Landis Book Project: Bart Van der Schelling: Singing, undated (Box 2, Audiocassette 66- 70, Box 5, Cd 66- 70)
  - Unrelated to Landis Book Project: Bart Van der Schelling and Others: Singing, Oct 13, 1968 (Box 2, Audiocassette 66- 71, Box 5, Cd 66- 71)